export const Data = {
  en: [
    { 
      id: 1,
      question:'What os Netflix?',
      answer: 'Netflix is a streaming service that offers a wide variety of award-winning TV shows, movies, anime, documentaries, and more on thousands of internet-connected devices.You can watch as much as you want, whenever you want without a single commercial – all for one low monthly price. Theres always something new to discover and new TV shows and movies are added every week!',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question:'How much does Netflix cost?',
      answer: 'Watch Netflix on your smartphone, tablet, Smart TV, laptop, or streaming device, all for one fixed monthly fee. Plans range from EGP120 to EGP200 a month. No extra costs, no contracts.'
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question:'Where can I watch?',
      answer: 'Watch anywhere, anytime. Sign in with your Netflix account to watch instantly on the web at netflix.com from your personal computer or on any internet-connected device that offers the Netflix app, including smart TVs, smartphones, tablets, streaming media players and game consoles.You can also download your favorite shows with the iOS, Android, or Windows 10 app. Use downloads to watch while you are on the go and without an internet connection. Take Netflix with you anywhere.',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question:'How do I cancel?',
      answer: 'Netflix is flexible. There are no pesky contracts and no commitments. You can easily cancel your account online in two clicks. There are no cancellation fees – start or stop your account anytime.',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question:'What can I watch on Netflix?',
      answer: 'Netflix has an extensive library of feature films, documentaries, TV shows, anime, award-winning Netflix originals, and more. Watch as much as you want, anytime you want.',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question:'Is Netflix good for kids?',
      answer: 'The Netflix Kids experience is included in your membership to give parents control while kids enjoy family-friendly TV shows and movies in their own space.Kids profiles come with PIN-protected parental controls that let you restrict the maturity rating of content kids can watch and block specific titles you donot want kids to see.',
    },
  ],
  ar:[
    { 
      id: 1,
      question:'؟Netflix ما هي خدمة',
      answer: 'Netflix هي خدمة بث تقدّم مجموعة متنوعة من العروض التلفزيونية والأفلام وأعمال الأنيمي الوثائقيات وغيرها من الأعمال الحائزة على جوائز من خلال الآلاف من الأجهزة المتصلة بالإنترنت. ويمكنك مشاهدة كل ما تريد وقتما تشاء، بدون إعلانات تجارية - وكل ذلك مقابل سعر شهري منخفض. ستجد دومًا شيئًا جديدًا لتكتشفه، حيث يتم إضافة عروض تلفزيونية وأفلام جديدة كل أسبوع!',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question:'؟Netflix كم تبلغ تكلفة',
      answer: 'شاهد Netflix على هاتفك الذكي أو الكمبيوتر اللوحي أو التلفزيون الذكي أو الكمبيوتر المحمول أو جهاز البث، وكل ذلك مقابل رسم شهري ثابت. تتراوح أسعار الخطط بين 120 ج.م.‎ و 200 ج.م.‎ في الشهر. بدون تكلفة إضافية، وبدون عقود.'
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question:'أين يمكنني أن أشاهد؟',
      answer: 'استمتع بالمشاهدة حيثما شئت ووقتما شئت. سجّل الدخول باستخدام حسابك على Netflix لتستمع بالمشاهدة الفورية على الويب عبر الموقع الإلكتروني netflix.com من الكمبيوتر الشخصي أو على أي جهاز متصل بالإنترنت مثبت عليه تطبيق Netflix، مثل أجهزة التلفزيون الذكية أو الهواتف الذكية أو أجهزة الكمبيوتر اللوحية أو مشغلات بث الوسائط أو أجهزة التحكم بالألعاب.يمكنك أيضًا تنزيل عروضك المُفضلة عبر التطبيق الذي يعمل على أنظمة التشغيل iOS أو Android أو Windows 10. استخدم ميزة التنزيلات للمشاهدة أثناء التنقل، دون الحاجة إلى الاتصال بالإنترنت. اصطحب NETFLIX معك حيثما شئت.',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question:'كيف أقوم بالالغاء؟',
      answer: 'تتسم خدمة Netflix بالمرونة. بلا عقود مزعجة وبلا التزامات. يمكنك إلغاء حسابك بكل سهولة عبر الإنترنت بنقرتين. لا رسوم للإلغاء، قم ببدء حسابك أو إيقافه في أي وقت.',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question:'؟Netflix ما الذي يممكنني مشاهدته علي',
      answer: 'تتوفر لدى Netflix مكتبة ضخمة من الأفلام الروائية والوثائقيات والعروض التلفزيونية والأنيمي وأعمال Netflix الأصلية الحائزة على الجوائز، وغيرها الكثير. شاهد كل ما تريد، متى شئت.',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question:'ملائمة للأطفال؟ Netflix هل',
      answer: 'تمنح تجربة Netflix للأطفال، والمُندرجة ضمن عضويتك، الأهل إمكانية التحكم بما يشاهده الأطفال خلال استمتاعهم بمشاهدة العروض التلفزيونية والأفلام الملائمة لجميع أفراد العائلة ضمن الملف الشخصي المُخصص لهم.وبفضل عناصر الرقابة الأبوية المحمية برمز PIN للملفات الشخصية للأطفال، يستطيع الأهل تقييد المحتوى الذي يمكن للأطفال مشاهدته وفق تصنيف نضج معين، فضلًا عن حظر عناوين محددة لا يرغب الأهل أن يشاهدها الأطفال.',
    },
  ]
}